zatse.in 2014-08-11

# Privacy Policy | ZatSe

** Untitled document

Majestic IT Services Ltd (MITSL) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. This policy only applies to the practices of companies that MITSL owns or controls and the network of sites operated by it. 

The following tends to disclose how the information provided by USERS (you) is collected, protected and used. This Policy is however subject to change. MITSL reserves the right to make modifications and updations in this privacy policy statement from time to time, the notice of which shall be published on MITSL’s website. You are requested to check for changes in the Privacy Policy from time to time. 

**Collection and Use of Information**

MITSL collects information from you that provides us with your personal & business information when you register to gain access to our services, when you use any of our services or products, conduct transactions at the time you visit our pages and web sites and when you take part in promotions of any kind run by us, with or without sponsors. The promotions run by us, that are with the support of or are jointly run with third party Sponsors, might require us to share the information collected during the said promotion with the Sponsor. A User not wanting us to share such information with the Sponsors is requested not to take part in the promotion. Data collected through User registration and/or their usage of our network of sites allows us to protect their personal and business information based on their account settings and customize their experience.

When you register with or access our Service, you are required to give your (his/her/it’s) name, email address, address, birth date, gender, occupation, business information and other personal details. Once you register, you are  deemed to have given your consent to MITSL to publish the desired business & personal details throughout its network of sites, including but not limited to, business directory, catalogs etc.

When you register with MITSL and sign in to use our services, you are no longer anonymous to us. MITSL server’s automatically record information when you visit any of our websites or use any of our services or products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, software and hardware attributes, the page you request and the date and time of your request. MITSL only collects this type of information to compile usage statistics on an anonymous basis. MITSL does not collect IP address data to identify you.

MITSL through its website provides information based services on any type of business, industry, individual, profession or Government establishment to businesses and the public at large. We do this by making your information available on our database and making the same available to those requesting for it. Such display or making available of information may result in the you being contacted by third party(ies) which may or may not be of interest to the you. MITSL does not have any control over the party(ies) contacting you and does not take any responsibility for the same.  We also use this information to customise the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you through email, phone or otherwise, conduct research, and provide anonymous reports to internal personnel and external clients.

**Sharing of Information  **

MITSL respects your privacy. MITSL will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties or non affiliated entities unless it is with your permission or to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services that you may have requested or under the following circumstances, and in all the given circumstances you shall be deemed to have given consent for the same:

MITSL may release the personal information if compelled by law or, in good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-parties, or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of employees of MITSL, its users or the general public.

Provide the information to trusted partners that work on behalf of or with MITSL under separate confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to assist MITSL in communicating with you about offers from us and our marketing partners.

**  Transfer your information in case MITSL is acquired by or merged with another company.**

MITSL may disclose your personal and business data to other entities belonging to MITSL and promoter group companies to the extent such disclosure is not incompatible to the purposes for which the data are collected as mentioned above.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit the website, when you visit the website again, the cookies allow that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. MITSL uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use MITSL services in order to improve the quality of our services. MITSL lets other companies that show advertisements on some of its network sites and pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MITSL's cookies. Unless you input your personal data onto our website you cannot be identified and remain anonymous.

**Confidentiality and Security**

MITSL takes appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of data over a network and all other unlawful forms of processing. MITSL takes all such measures, which are commercially viable and necessary, to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risks represented by the processing and the nature of the data to be processed. It limits access to personal information about you to employees who it believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**Right to Update, Correct and Delete  **

You have the right to ask MITSL for the details of the information it holds about you. In addition, you have the right to correct or delete any information it holds about you. In case you wish to know which information MITSL holds about you or wish MITSL to correct, update or delete any such information please contact it on the details given in Contact Us below.

**Authorisation**

You acknowledge that you are disclosing the information voluntarily. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information while registering with us. You may refrain from disclosing any information. However, if the minimum information required for registration is not made available then your registration process would be incomplete and you would not be able to avail of our services.

**Contact Us  **

We welcome your concerns, suggestions, comments etc for this privacy policy statement, in case you wish to do the same or wish to exercise your right to seek an updation or deletion of your information, as mentioned above, please do not hesitate to contact us at:

Majestic IT Services Limited 

Logix Omnia

Ground Floor

A-110 Sector 4, Noida

**
